Oh my God
Laura
That gold bracelet is huge
Must have cost a lot
Son
It's such a waste of money
You should return it
Just wear it if you like it
I make money
Just to make you happy
Lewes is so thoughtful
Listen to him
I saw your bag on my phone
It's some Louie Vee
Costs forty to fifty grand
A big gold watch
A tri-fold phone
That's so impressive
Lewes must have bought all these
Oh
I told him not to spend the money
Any phone works the same
But Lewes wouldn't listen
Such a big spender
These days
How many young people
Would spend so much
on their parents
Lewes is so devoted
Tell me about it
If he were my son
I'd be over the moon
Hey Lewes
You make so much money
Why not buy a good car
You just bought a van
I didn't make much profit after costs
A van is fine
It's practical
For buying feed in the future
And moving froglets
Lewes is so practical
Unlike some people
Who make a little money
And forget their roots
I said it back then
It wouldn't last
And look what happened
What goes up
Must come down
Landon and Laura
You'll enjoy a good life now
So he made a few bucks
What's he showing off for
A son-in-law is half a son
Daniel owes so much money
As his brother-in-law
He should at least pitch in